<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">GCECT APP</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="gate_rank">%s: %d</string>
    <string name="research_dev_p1">The Institute has highly qualified faculty members where 35% of them are Doctorate Degree Holders.
        The rest are Post Graduate Degree holders out of which most of them are pursuing their Ph.D degrees.
        Over the last one year, the college has produced 5 Ph.Ds from both engineering and science departments.\n\n
        The faculty has contributed more than 100 research papers and presentations in Indian as well as International journals.
        Besides, several Research and Development projects sponsored by Department of Science and Technology(DST), University Grants Commission(UGC), All India Council of Technical Education(AICTE) etc are running some of which have been successfully completed.
        All these accomplishments definitely prove that this institute is a ground for nurturing intellects.
        The faculty members have contributed to books by reputed publishers, research papers in international journals of repute and international conference proceedings.\n\n
        The institute has also received grant from the World Bank in the TEQIP-1 Phase for various developmental projects.\n\n
        This grant has been spent for:\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="consultancy_item_text">Consultancy activities are carried out by faculty members of various departments. They are provided to different organizations by way of auditing and as technical experts during audit of ISO 9001:2008 QMS, ISO 14001:2004 Ems and ISO 18001:2007 OHSAS.</string>
    <string name="collaboration_details">How has the College’s collaboration with other agencies impacted the visibility, identity and diversity of activities on the campus? To what extent has the College benefited academically and financially because of collaborations?</string>
    <string name="research_dev_p2">
        ⚫ Development of Infrastructure.\n
        ⚫ New Laboratory equipments.\n
        ⚫ Maintenance and repair of old laboratory equipments.\n
        ⚫ Funding for research and lectures attended by faculty in foreign universities.\n
        ⚫ Aim towards community development implementation of tribal development plan for students and overall growth.
    </string>
    <string name="research_dev_p3">A detailed list of Research Projects under various departments which are running and some of which have been successfully completed have been listed below:</string>
    <string name="r_d_project_title">Title : %s</string>
    <string name="r_d_project_funding_agency">Funding Agency : %s</string>
    <string name="r_d_project_amount">Amount: %s</string>
    <string name="r_d_project_status">Status: %s</string>
    <string name="r_d_teacher_detail">%s,\n%s</string>
    <string name="s_v_p1">Being one of the most sought after Higher Education Institutions in India, Government College Of Engineering and Ceramic Technology takes pride in introducing a journal named SCIENTIFIC VOYAGE that throws light on significant areas in Science, Engineering, Management and Technology. The journal enables publication of pre-eminent research work by Researchers, Acamedicians, and Scientists pertaining to varied disciplines.</string>
    <string name="s_v_p2">Government College of Engineering and Ceramic Technology was established in 1941 by Professor Sasadhar Ray who was an eminent and educationist and the first Principal of the college. At that time the college was named as Bengal Ceramic Institute Calcutta, which later on flowered into College of Ceramic Technology. Professor Ray was one of the pioneers in spreading ceramic education in India. He obtained his M.Sc. degree in Physics in 1930, as a student of Prof. Satyendranath Bose, from the University of Dacca having been place first in Class. He was a research scholar under Prof. K. S. Krishnan-F.R.S. in the Indian Association for the Cultivation of Science and served as a supervisor in Peripatetic Demonstration for Scheme of the Govt. of Bengal to popularize the ceramic manufacturing processes in the villages. He also worked for a brief period in the Industrial Research Laboratory, Dept. of Industries, Government of West Bengal.</string>
    <string name="s_v_p3">The college started with certificate and diploma courses in Ceramic Technology with six other different courses to train people for various ceramic industries in the eastern and other regions of India. Prof. Roy organized a commercial Training- cum- Production unit at the institute to provide employment through practical training to the students. He formulated many developmental schemes with their successful implementation and introduced the concept of self- employment in the institute to cope with the problem of growing unemployment in the country. He was the pioneer in India to manufacture bone chinawares using indigenous raw materials on commercial basis and glazed pottery, sanitary wares, tiles and low-tension insulators from Gangetic silt. His contribution to ceramic education and industry has gone for and near within India and round the globe.</string>
    <string name="s_v_p4">In the year 1962, B. Sc (Tech.) degree course in Ceramic Technology under the University of Calcutta was introduced in the institute, which was then renamed as College of Ceramic Technology and was undertaken by the Govt. of West Bengal. At that time more emphasis was given on Traditional Ceramics. Traditional consists of pottery including materials, cement, etc. and traditional glasses for windows and containers/bottles including crystal glasses and of course the infamous optical glasses for our eyes and cameras.</string>
    <string name="s_v_p5">Then came Dr. B. N. Samaddar as the Principal of the College, who was trained in MIT, USA. He brought a sophisticated touch of modern ceramics like Nuclear Ceramics, Space Ceramics, Electronic and Magnetic Ceramics, Bio-Ceramics, Piezoelectrics and Ferroelectrics by continuous enriching the courses with a strong emphasis on Materials Science.</string>
    <string name="s_v_p6">This college has seen the addition of two new B.Tech courses in Information Technology and Computer Science and Engineering which was initiated under the West Bengal University of Technology in the year 2000 and 2001 as well as the M.Tech course in Ceramic Technology which was introduced in the year 2006. The B.Tech and M.Tech courses of Ceramic Technology and the B.Tech course in Information Technology has already been accredited by the National Board of Accreditation (NBA). The institute has also recently gained approval from AICTE to begin the M. Tech. course in Information Technology.</string>
    <string name="nss_p">NSS Unit of Govt. College of Engineering and Ceramic Technology has celebrated International Yoga Day on 21-June-2021 using Google Meet. Yogacharya Parthasarathi Banerjee of SHIVANANDA YOGASHRAM, Kolkata demonstrated various techniques of yoga by which diseases can be cured and controlled. Screenshots and video-link are given herewith.</string>
    <string name="placement_cell_p">The Training and Placement Cell of this Institute has, for several decades, successfully met the needs of different sectors of the Industry. The Campus Recruitment Programme, organised every year in the penultimate semester of the B.Tech Programme has successfully met the HR needs of leading recruiters for the past few decades.The Placement programme is also organized as a central activity for all the Government Engineering College students in and around Kolkata. With their diversity and well-balanced technical and soft skills, the students of this Institute are well equipped to contribute towards the success of organisations. Many employers who recruit at GCECT have been doing so for decades, and they return because they have had great success with their recruits.\n\n
    The Training and Placement Officer who is a senior faculty of this Institute and a team of departmental faculty members are all working to build up a good relationship with different industries through Seminars/Workshops/Industry visits/Invited talk/Project and Consultancies throughout the year. The rigours of study at this Institute, coupled with lab practice and balanced exposure to the Industry as well as co and extracurricular activities on campus through a range of student clubs and societies, brings out the best from the students and prepares them well for challenging leadership roles. GCECT alumni contributing in positions of highest responsibility, across the globe, are a witness to this.
    </string>
    <string name="placement_overview_p">The placement programme of GCECT has been moving from strength to strength through nurturing of value added relationships over the years. Every year, new milestones are established which speaks well for the strengths of this institute?s student community as well as the diversity of academic programmes offered.\n\n
        The final year students of Ceramic Technology have already undergone 100% recruitment in various renowned companies like Saint Gobain Glass, Jindal South West Steel., Essar Steel, Steel Authority of India., Grindwell Norton, MECON, Tata Refractories and more. The students of final year, IT and CSE departments have also been successful in getting through software giants such as TCS., Cognizant ,Wipro, Infosys, Tech. Mahindra, Accenture,Tata Elxsi and many more. The year 2020 saw the B.Tech students of Ceramic Technology getting the highest salary of about Rs.7.5 lakh and an average salary of Rs.3.00 lakh. The companies that visited this college for recruiting B.Tech. students of IT and CSE departments in the year 2020 had been offered the highest salary of about 4.50 lakh and the average salary about 3.00 lakh</string>
    <string name="history_page">Our College of Ceramic Technology was established in 1941 by Professor Sasadhar Ray who was an eminent and educationist and the first Principal of the college. At that time the college was named as Bengal Ceramic Institute Calcutta, which later on flowered into College of Ceramic Technology. Professor Ray was one of the pioneers in spreading ceramic education in India. He obtained his M.Sc. degree in Physics in 1930, as a student of Prof. Satyendranath Bose, from the University of Dacca having been place first in Class. He was a research scholar under Prof. K. S. Krishnan-F.R.S. in the Indian Association for the Cultivation of Science and served as a supervisor in Peripatetic Demonstration for Scheme of the Govt. of Bengal to popularize the ceramic manufacturing processes in the villages. He also worked for a brief period in the Industrial Research Laboratory, Dept. of Industries, Government of West Bengal.\n\n
    The college started with certificate and diploma courses in Ceramic Technology with six other different courses to train people for various ceramic industries in the eastern and other regions of India. Prof. Roy organized a commercial Training- cum- Production unit at the institute to provide employment through practical training to the students. He formulated many developmental schemes with their successful implementation and introduced the concept of self- employment in the institute to cope with the problem of growing unemployment in the country. He was the pioneer in India to manufacture bone chinawares using indigenous raw materials on commercial basis and glazed pottery, sanitary wares, tiles and low-tension insulators from Gangetic silt. His contribution to ceramic education and industry has gone for and near within India and round the globe.\n\n
    In the year 1962, B. Sc (Tech.) degree course in Ceramic Technology under the University of Calcutta was introduced in the institute, which was then renamed as College of Ceramic Technology and was undertaken by the Govt. of West Bengal. At that time more emphasis was given on Traditional Ceramics. Traditional consists of pottery including materials, cement, etc. and traditional glasses for windows and containers/bottles including crystal glasses and of course the infamous optical glasses for our eyes and cameras.\n\n
    Then came Dr. B. N. Samaddar as the Principal of the College, who was trained in MIT, USA. He brought a sophisticated touch of modern ceramics like Nuclear Ceramics, Space Ceramics, Electronic and Magnetic Ceramics, Bio-Ceramics, Piezoelectrics and Ferroelectrics by continuous enriching the courses with a strong emphasis on Materials Science.\n\n
    This college has seen the addition of two new B.Tech courses in Information Technology and Computer Science and Engineering which was initiated under the West Bengal University of Technology in the year 2000 and 2001 as well as the M.Tech course in Ceramic Technology which was introduced in the year 2006. The B.Tech and M.Tech courses of Ceramic Technology and the B.Tech course in Information Technology has already been accredited by the National Board of Accreditation (NBA). The institute has also recently gained approval from AICTE to begin the M. Tech. course in Information Technology.</string>
    <string name="vision_and_mission_p1">To cultivate excellence in various fields of engineering and technology by imparting core knowledge to the students and to transform the institution into a center of academic excellence and advanced research apart from producing skilled technologist.</string>
    <string name="vision_and_mission_p2_1">To impart quality technical education that will produce globally competitive engineers and technologists.</string>
    <string name="vision_and_mission_p2_2">To inculcate entrepreneurial skill and leadership quality amongst potential students.</string>
    <string name="vision_and_mission_p2_3">To stress upon acquiring advanced knowledge and research acumen among faculties and students.</string>
    <string name="vision_and_mission_p2_4">To create compassionate, responsible and innovative global citizen.</string>
    <string name="info_act">Nodal Information Officer : Mr. Jayanta Chowdhury \nGCECT \nMob # 9477239771 \nEmail : gcect.registrar@gmail.com </string>
    <string name="the_institute_p1">
        An educational institute is a place where young minds are nurtured in the best possible way, where their skills are developed in a specific field. A good foothold is therefore essential, and the Govt. College of Engineering and Ceramic Technology is such an institute, where students are given the best platform to exhibit their talents. We take this opportunity, to introduce ourselves, as one of the leading government engineering colleges under the Department of Higher Education in the eastern part of India.\n\n
        From its humble beginning as the Bengal Ceramic Institute in 1942, renamed as the College of Ceramic Technology in 1962, and further renamed as the Govt. College of Engineering and Ceramic Technology in 2005, the college is entering the 80th glorious year of its academic life. It is indeed a time to celebrate, to introspect, to consolidate and to plan for its future. The uniqueness of this institute is that, it is the oldest institute for imparting technical education in Ceramic Science and Engineering, in the Eastern Part of India and the only institute offering a full fledged Undergraduate and Postgraduate course in Ceramic Technology in the state of West Bengal. This college has seen the addition of two new B.Tech courses in Information Technology and Computer Science and Engineering which was initiated under\n\n
        the West Bengal University of Technology in the year 2000 and 2001 as well as the M.Tech course in Ceramic Technology which was introduced in the year 2006. The B.Tech and M.Tech courses of Ceramic Technology and the B.Tech course in Information Technology has already been accredited by the National Board of Accreditation (NBA).\n\n
        The college has reached its magnificence under the admirable guidance and leadership of eminent academicians of international repute. The institute is presently headed by Prof.(Dr.) Saikat Maitra, under whose able guidance and leadership, the institute has been able to make commendable achievements.\n\n
        The academic program of this institute presently comprises of the mentioned B.Tech courses which has an intake of 48 students each and M.Tech course with an intake of 18 students. The institute has recently gained approval from AICTE to begin the M. Tech. course in Information Technology with a sanctioned intake of 18 students. The institute can boast of well equipped workshop and laboratories, which is essential for the scheduled academic curriculum and research activities operational at the institute. Besides other departmental laboratories, special mention is needed for sophisticated and specialized labs developed such as the Thin Film lab, Nano-Materials and Sol-gel Lab of the Ceramic Department and VLSI, Image Processing, GIS and the Computer Vision Lab of the Information Technology department. Another feather in the cap is the addition of a most modern Language Lab for English Communication Skill and Personality Development as well as the EDUSAT lab with Virtual Learning capability of our students. It is worth mentioning that the entire campus is connected to the internet for 24 hours through NKN Leased Line (100 mbps) connectivity which is accessible from all computers in the institute.\n\n
        The Institute has highly qualified faculty members where 35% of them are Doctorate Degree Holders. The rest are Post Graduate Degree holders out of which most of them are pursuing their Ph.D degrees. Over the last five years, the college has produced 5 Ph.Ds from both engineering and science departments. The faculty has contributed more than 100 research papers and presentations in Indian as well as International journals. Besides, several Research and Development projects sponsored by D.S.T, U.G.C, AICTE etc are running some of which have been successfully completed. All these accomplishments definitely prove that this institute is a ground for nurturing intellects.\n\n
        The institute has also received grant from the World Bank in the TEQIP One Phase for various developmental projects. This grant has been spent for:
    </string>
    <string name="the_institute_p2">Development of Infrastructure.</string>
    <string name="the_institute_p3">New Laboratory equipments.</string>
    <string name="the_institute_p4">Maintenance and repair of old laboratory equipments.</string>
    <string name="the_institute_p5">Funding for research and lectures attended by faculty in foreign universities.</string>
    <string name="the_institute_p6">Aim towards community development and over all growth.</string>
    <string name="the_institute_p7">The Institute has collaborated with reputed institutions at national and international level for postgraduate, project and Ph.D programmes.The Petronus University of Malaysia, Northern University in Saudi Arabia, Curtin University in Australia, Jadavpur University, Calcutta University, Presidency University, CGCRI, Saha Institute of Nuclear Physics are the ones to name a few. The institute has undertaken different technical training programmes for the self employment of the unemployed youth under Services to the Community and Economy Scheme of World Bank funded Project TEQIP. The institute also promotes active students participation in NSS programme. It is also worth mentioning that college is about to get academic autonomy from the University Grants Commission and has already gained part financial autonomy after completing its TEQIP-1 phase.\n\n
        The institute library can boast of more than 17,000 books as well as 15 or more National and International Journals covering various arenas of research and study.\n\n
        The Institute is proud of its students who are amongst the top rankers in the West Bengal Joint Entrance Examination. The successful students to have qualified the GATE examination this year has been about 45% in the Ceramic department, 40% in Computer Science and Engg and about 25% in Information Technology departments. The final year students of Ceramic Technology has already undergone 100% recruitment in various renowned companies like Saint Gobain Glass, Jindal South West Steel., Essar Steel, Steel Authority of India., Grindwell Norton, MECON, Tata Refractories and more. The students of final year, IT and CSE departments have also been successful in getting through software giants such as TCS., Cognizant ,Wipro, Infosys, Tech. Mahindra, Accenture, Tata Elxsi and many more. Many of the students of this institute are pursuing higher studies in reputed national institutions like the IITs and NITs and many have gone abroad to Universities like Sheffield, University of Florida, University of Washington, Arizona State University, Drexel University (Pennsylvania), University of Cincinnati to name a few.\n\n
        Over the years the college has grown and learnt to dream. It strives hard to become a “Centre of Excellence” in education which, in keeping with the rich heritage of India, will stress the simultaneous development of Body, Mind and Soul and endeavour to create compassionate, responsible and innovative global citizens who are commited to the development of India. These are the true objectives of the Institution. The development is still on.
    </string>
    <string name="workshop_seminar">Workshop Seminar</string>
    <string name="welfare_association">Welfare Association</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="allow_download_permission_message">Please allow all permission to Download</string>
    <string name="download_complete">Download Complete</string>
    <string name="downloading" tools:ignore="TypographyEllipsis">DownLoading...</string>
    <string name="download_percentage_completed">DownLoad : %d</string>
    <string name="error_at_page_number">Error at page: %d</string>
    <string name="placement_overview">Placement Overview</string>
    <string name="placement_call">Placement Cell</string>
    <string name="placement_call_email">For Correspondence with Training and Placement Cell: gcect@rediffmail.com</string>
    <string name="title_empty_error_message">OOPs!! Note Title can\'t be empty</string>
    <string name="history">HISTORY</string>
    <string name="exam_schedule">Exam Schedules</string>
    <string name="csi_student_chapter">CSI Student Chapter</string>
    <string name="view_less">VIEW LESS</string>
    <string name="view_more">VIEW MORE</string>
    <string name="location_contact_us"><![CDATA[Govt. College Of Engineering \n & Ceramic Technology 73, Abinash \nChandra Banerjee Lane, Kolkata-700 010]]></string>
    <string name="phone_contact_us">\t 2370 1263, 2363 3674, 2363 3675</string>
    <string name="fax_contact_us">\t 2370 1264, 2363 36745</string>
    <string name="email_contact_us">\t principal@gcect.ac.in , \n \t gcectwb@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="cse_p1">The B.Tech. course is duly approved by the All India Council for Technical Education (AICTE), Government of India and the Department of Higher Education, Government of West Bengal. The duration of study of this course is 4 years (8 semesters) and total intake in each discipline is 40+8 (lateral entry) students. The B.Tech course in Ceramic Technology is NBA accredited.</string>
    <string name="cse_p2">"The Institute has been offering a full time postgraduate course leading to M. Tech in Ceramic Technology since 2006. The sanctioned intake of students for the M.Tech course is 18.The M.Tech. course in Ceramic Technology is NBA accredited.  "</string>
    <string name="cse_p3">This academic department offers guidance and facilites for Ph.D.programe. The Institute has collaborated with reputed institutions at national and international level for postgraduate, project and Ph.D programmes.The Petronus University of Malaysia, Northern University in Saudi Arabia, Curtin University in Australia, Jadavpur University, Calcutta University, Presidency University, CGCRI, Saha Institute of Nuclear Physics are the ones to name a few.</string>
    <string name="cs_p1"><![CDATA[The Department of Computer Science and Engineering, established in the year 2001, is amongst the youngest amongst the three departments of the institute. At present, the department is offering a 4-year B. Tech. course in Computer Science & Engineering, with an intake of 40 students in the first year and 8 more as lateral entry in the second year. As one of the youngest departments, it is reputed for producing the best quality software engineers who serve in leading companies, not only in India but also abroad. The students have an in-depth exposure to computing environment consisting of state-of-the-art machines in different laboratories.\n\n  The B.Tech. course is duly approved by the All India Council for Technical Education (AICTE), Government of India and the Department of Higher Education, Government of West Bengal.]]></string>
    <string name="gcect">GCECT</string>
    <string name="administration">ADMINISTRATION</string>
    <string name="key_administration">KEY ADMINISTRATION</string>
    <string name="principal_prof_dr_krishnendu_chakrabarty">Principal: Prof.(Dr) Krishnendu Chakrabarty</string>
    <string name="registrar_nshri_jayanta_choudhury">Registrar:\nShri Jayanta Choudhury</string>
    <string name="accounts_officer_nshri_kanti_kamal_sen">Accounts Officer:\nShri Kanti Kamal Sen</string>
    <string name="governing_body">GOVERNING BODY</string>
    <string name="prof_binay_k_dutta_chariman_west_bengal_pollution_control_board_chairman">Prof. Binay K. Dutta, Chariman, West Bengal Pollution Control Board – Chairman</string>
    <string name="accounts_officer_n_shri_kanti_kamal_sen">Accounts Officer:\n Shri Kanti Kamal Sen</string>
    <string name="registrar_n_shri_jayanta_choudhury">Registrar:\n Shri Jayanta Choudhury</string>
</resources>
