<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GCECT APP</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="gate_rank">%s: %d</string>
    <string name="research_dev_p1">The Institute has highly qualified faculty members where 35% of them are Doctorate Degree Holders.
        The rest are Post Graduate Degree holders out of which most of them are pursuing their Ph.D degrees.
        Over the last one year, the college has produced 5 Ph.Ds from both engineering and science departments.\n\n
        The faculty has contributed more than 100 research papers and presentations in Indian as well as International journals.
        Besides, several Research and Development projects sponsored by Department of Science and Technology(DST), University Grants Commission(UGC), All India Council of Technical Education(AICTE) etc are running some of which have been successfully completed.
        All these accomplishments definitely prove that this institute is a ground for nurturing intellects.
        The faculty members have contributed to books by reputed publishers, research papers in international journals of repute and international conference proceedings.\n\n
        The institute has also received grant from the World Bank in the TEQIP-1 Phase for various developmental projects.\n\n
        This grant has been spent for:\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="research_dev_p2">
        ⚫ Development of Infrastructure.\n
        ⚫ New Laboratory equipments.\n
        ⚫ Maintenance and repair of old laboratory equipments.\n
        ⚫ Funding for research and lectures attended by faculty in foreign universities.\n
        ⚫ Aim towards community development implementation of tribal development plan for students and overall growth.
    </string>
    <string name="research_dev_p3">A detailed list of Research Projects under various departments which are running and some of which have been successfully completed have been listed below:</string>
    <string name="r_d_project_title">Title : %s</string>
    <string name="r_d_project_funding_agency">Funding Agency : %s</string>
    <string name="r_d_project_amount">Amount: %s</string>
    <string name="r_d_project_status">Status: %s</string>
    <string name="r_d_teacher_detail">%s,\n%s</string>
    <string name="s_v_p1">Being one of the most sought after Higher Education Institutions in India, Government College Of Engineering and Ceramic Technology takes pride in introducing a journal named SCIENTIFIC VOYAGE that throws light on significant areas in Science, Engineering, Management and Technology. The journal enables publication of pre-eminent research work by Researchers, Acamedicians, and Scientists pertaining to varied disciplines.</string>
    <string name="s_v_p2">Goverment College of Engineering and Ceramic Technology was established in 1941 by Professor Sasadhar Ray who was an eminent and educationist and the first Principal of the college. At that time the college was named as Bengal Ceramic Institute Calcutta, which later on flowered into College of Ceramic Technology. Professor Ray was one of the pioneers in spreading ceramic education in India. He obtained his M.Sc. degree in Physics in 1930, as a student of Prof. Satyendranath Bose, from the University of Dacca having been place first in Class. He was a research scholar under Prof. K. S. Krishnan-F.R.S. in the Indian Association for the Cultivation of Science and served as a supervisor in Peripatetic Demonstration for Scheme of the Govt. of Bengal to popularize the ceramic manufacturing processes in the villages. He also worked for a brief period in the Industrial Research Laboratory, Dept. of Industries, Government of West Bengal.</string>
    <string name="s_v_p3">The college started with certificate and diploma courses in Ceramic Technology with six other different courses to train people for various ceramic industries in the eastern and other regions of India. Prof. Roy organized a commercial Training- cum- Production unit at the institute to provide employment through practical training to the students. He formulated many developmental schemes with their successful implementation and introduced the concept of self- employment in the institute to cope with the problem of growing unemployment in the country. He was the pioneer in India to manufacture bone chinawares using indigenous raw materials on commercial basis and glazed pottery, sanitary wares, tiles and low-tension insulators from Gangetic silt. His contribution to ceramic education and industry has gone for and near within India and round the globe.</string>
    <string name="s_v_p4">In the year 1962, B. Sc (Tech.) degree course in Ceramic Technology under the University of Calcutta was introduced in the institute, which was then renamed as College of Ceramic Technology and was undertaken by the Govt. of West Bengal. At that time more emphasis was given on Traditional Ceramics. Traditional consists of pottery including materials, cement, etc. and traditional glasses for windows and containers/bottles including crystal glasses and of course the infamous optical glasses for our eyes and cameras.</string>
    <string name="s_v_p5">Then came Dr. B. N. Samaddar as the Principal of the College, who was trained in MIT, USA. He brought a sophisticated touch of modern ceramics like Nuclear Ceramics, Space Ceramics, Electronic and Magnetic Ceramics, Bio-Ceramics, Piezoelectrics and Ferroelectrics by continuous enriching the courses with a strong emphasis on Materials Science.</string>
    <string name="s_v_p6">This college has seen the addition of two new B.Tech courses in Information Technology and Computer Science and Engineering which was initiated under the West Bengal University of Technology in the year 2000 and 2001 as well as the M.Tech course in Ceramic Technology which was introduced in the year 2006. The B.Tech and M.Tech courses of Ceramic Technology and the B.Tech course in Information Technology has already been accredited by the National Board of Accreditation (NBA). The institute has also recently gained approval from AICTE to begin the M. Tech. course in Information Technology.</string>
    <string name="nss_p">NSS Unit of Govt. College of Engineering and Ceramic Technology has celebrated International Yoga Day on 21-June-2021 using Google Meet. Yogacharya Parthasarathi Banerjee of SHIVANANDA YOGASHRAM, Kolkata demonstrated various techniques of yoga by which diseases can be cured and controlled. Screenshots and video-link are given herewith.</string>
    <string name="placement_cell_p">The Training and Placement Cell of this Institute has, for several decades, successfully met the needs of different sectors of the Industry. The Campus Recruitment Programme, organised every year in the penultimate semester of the B.Tech Programme has successfully met the HR needs of leading recruiters for the past few decades.The Placement programme is also organized as a central activity for all the Government Engineering College students in and around Kolkata. With their diversity and well-balanced technical and soft skills, the students of this Institute are well equipped to contribute towards the success of organisations. Many employers who recruit at GCECT have been doing so for decades, and they return because they have had great success with their recruits.\n\n
    The Training and Placement Officer who is a senior faculty of this Institute and a team of departmental faculty members are all working to build up a good relationship with different industries through Seminars/Workshops/Industry visits/Invited talk/Project and Consultancies throughout the year. The rigours of study at this Institute, coupled with lab practice and balanced exposure to the Industry as well as co and extracurricular activities on campus through a range of student clubs and societies, brings out the best from the students and prepares them well for challenging leadership roles. GCECT alumni contributing in positions of highest responsibility, across the globe, are a witness to this.
    </string>
    <string name="placement_overview_p">The placement programme of GCECT has been moving from strength to strength through nurturing of value added relationships over the years. Every year, new milestones are established which speaks well for the strengths of this institute?s student community as well as the diversity of academic programmes offered.\n\n
        The final year students of Ceramic Technology have already undergone 100% recruitment in various renowned companies like Saint Gobain Glass, Jindal South West Steel., Essar Steel, Steel Authority of India., Grindwell Norton, MECON, Tata Refractories and more. The students of final year, IT and CSE departments have also been successful in getting through software giants such as TCS., Cognizant ,Wipro, Infosys, Tech. Mahindra, Accenture,Tata Elxsi and many more. The year 2020 saw the B.Tech students of Ceramic Technology getting the highest salary of about Rs.7.5 lakh and an average salary of Rs.3.00 lakh. The companies that visited this college for recruiting B.Tech. students of IT and CSE departments in the year 2020 had been offered the highest salary of about 4.50 lakh and the average salary about 3.00 lakh</string>
    <string name="history_page">Our College of Ceramic Technology was established in 1941 by Professor Sasadhar Ray who was an eminent and educationist and the first Principal of the college. At that time the college was named as Bengal Ceramic Institute Calcutta, which later on flowered into College of Ceramic Technology. Professor Ray was one of the pioneers in spreading ceramic education in India. He obtained his M.Sc. degree in Physics in 1930, as a student of Prof. Satyendranath Bose, from the University of Dacca having been place first in Class. He was a research scholar under Prof. K. S. Krishnan-F.R.S. in the Indian Association for the Cultivation of Science and served as a supervisor in Peripatetic Demonstration for Scheme of the Govt. of Bengal to popularize the ceramic manufacturing processes in the villages. He also worked for a brief period in the Industrial Research Laboratory, Dept. of Industries, Government of West Bengal.\n\n
    The college started with certificate and diploma courses in Ceramic Technology with six other different courses to train people for various ceramic industries in the eastern and other regions of India. Prof. Roy organized a commercial Training- cum- Production unit at the institute to provide employment through practical training to the students. He formulated many developmental schemes with their successful implementation and introduced the concept of self- employment in the institute to cope with the problem of growing unemployment in the country. He was the pioneer in India to manufacture bone chinawares using indigenous raw materials on commercial basis and glazed pottery, sanitary wares, tiles and low-tension insulators from Gangetic silt. His contribution to ceramic education and industry has gone for and near within India and round the globe.\n\n
    In the year 1962, B. Sc (Tech.) degree course in Ceramic Technology under the University of Calcutta was introduced in the institute, which was then renamed as College of Ceramic Technology and was undertaken by the Govt. of West Bengal. At that time more emphasis was given on Traditional Ceramics. Traditional consists of pottery including materials, cement, etc. and traditional glasses for windows and containers/bottles including crystal glasses and of course the infamous optical glasses for our eyes and cameras.\n\n
    Then came Dr. B. N. Samaddar as the Principal of the College, who was trained in MIT, USA. He brought a sophisticated touch of modern ceramics like Nuclear Ceramics, Space Ceramics, Electronic and Magnetic Ceramics, Bio-Ceramics, Piezoelectrics and Ferroelectrics by continuous enriching the courses with a strong emphasis on Materials Science.\n\n
    This college has seen the addition of two new B.Tech courses in Information Technology and Computer Science and Engineering which was initiated under the West Bengal University of Technology in the year 2000 and 2001 as well as the M.Tech course in Ceramic Technology which was introduced in the year 2006. The B.Tech and M.Tech courses of Ceramic Technology and the B.Tech course in Information Technology has already been accredited by the National Board of Accreditation (NBA). The institute has also recently gained approval from AICTE to begin the M. Tech. course in Information Technology.</string>
</resources>